http://www.madisonco.com/privacy-policy

Shop In-Stock Products
Madison Company will be closed Dec. 24th through 28th, Dec. 31st and Jan. 1st. We will resume normal operations on Jan. 4th. Happy Holidays!
Madison Company respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information Collected
If you request or submit information to Madison Company by sending an e-mail via the "mail to:" function or filling out our contact form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about Madison Company solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only the policy of Madison Company website and not the sites that users access via links from our site. Madison Company is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies
Please refer to the Madison Company cookie policy at www.madisonco.com/cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information
If you would like to have your personal information removed from Madison Company's records, please send an e–mail via the contact form, with "Remove personal information" in the comments field. To update, change, or correct your personal information, please send an e-mail via the contact form with the appropriate changes.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
Madison Company may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that Madison Company reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Madison Company and is effective as of February 12, 2012. This statement does not create an agreement between Madison Company and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
For inquiries, please contact:
Madison Company
27 Business Park Drive Branford, CT 06405
Phone: 203-488-4477 Toll-Free: 800-466-5383 Fax: 203-481-5036
info@madisonco.com
Find Your Sensor
Find your sensor:
